<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>wtf.tonho.omniget</id>
  <name>Omniget</name>
  <summary>Download media from multiple platforms</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer id="wtf.tonho">
    <name>Tonho</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>
      Omniget is a desktop application to download videos, courses, and media
      from platforms like YouTube, Udemy, Hotmart, Telegram, Instagram, TikTok,
      Twitter, Reddit, Twitch, Pinterest, Bluesky, and Vimeo.
    </p>
    <p>Features include:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Multi-platform media downloading</li>
      <li>Course downloading from Udemy and Hotmart</li>
      <li>Telegram media browser and batch downloader</li>
      <li>Media format conversion</li>
      <li>Queue management with concurrent downloads</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/tonhowtf/omniget</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/tonhowtf/omniget/issues</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/tonhowtf/omniget</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">wtf.tonho.omniget.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>omniget</binary>
  </provides>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main download interface</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tonhowtf/omniget/main/flatpak/screenshots/main.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#f4f4f4</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#131313</color>
  </branding>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="0.6.1" date="2026-05-12">
      <description>
        <p>YouTube playlist quality settings now respected. Per-video format picker hidden for playlists. Aria2c progress correctly reported in the queue (was stuck at 0% until completion). Quality chip shown on each queue item to confirm what's being downloaded.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.5.2" date="2026-05-06">
      <description>
        <p>Bruno</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.5.1" date="2026-05-05">
      <description>
        <p>Plugin loading: surface ABI-mismatch errors with a "reinstall" prompt instead of an endless "restart" loop (fixes #102), and show the underlying load error on the Marketplace card. i18n: replace hardcoded Portuguese strings in the study command palette with translated keys across all 8 locales.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.5.0" date="2026-05-03">
      <description>
        <p>Visual restructure: refreshed theme grid, reorganized settings, mascot celebrations with new "amazed" state, and gamified pets. Accessibility: aria-live regions on toasts. Reliability: torrent session shuts down gracefully on app exit, Pinterest regex validated at init. Tooling: single-command version bump, i18n keys auto-generated, multi-OS CI matrix.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.2" date="2026-04-14">
      <description>
        <p>Bug fixes and improvements.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.1" date="2026-04-13">
      <description>
        <p>Fix Instagram downloads failing with "Server returned HTML instead of media" when the primary extractors fell back to yt-dlp. The browser extension now requests wildcard host permissions only when the media sniffer is enabled, ships with an explicit allowlist for 13 supported platforms, and distinguishes the two popup toggles (open app vs. media detection) with separate icons. Native host logging redacts cookie values; cookie-domain mappings are now data-driven.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.0" date="2026-04-05">
      <description>
        <p>Plugin system release: courses, telegram, and convert plugins now ship independently via Marketplace. Version 0.4.0 enables the new plugin architecture.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.7" date="2026-03-18">
      <description>
        <p>35+ course platforms (Kiwify, Teachable, Kajabi, Skool, Pluralsight, MasterClass, Rocketseat, Estratégia, and more), Chinese platform support (Bilibili, Douyin, Xiaohongshu), P2P file transfer with iroh relay, TikTok quality fix, torrent file picker, cookie JSON import, and numerous bug fixes.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.6" date="2026-03-08">
      <description>
        <p>Light theme fixes, Greek language support, ffmpeg merge fix for downloads, performance improvements, and open folder button for completed downloads.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.4" date="2026-03-01">
      <description>
        <p>Fix hidden PowerShell window on clipboard copy, corrected flatpak build patches, and updated Linux build dependencies.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.3" date="2026-03-01">
      <description>
        <p>Dual-mode hotkey binding input, flatpak build fixes, and improvements.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.2" date="2026-02-27">
      <description>
        <p>Bug fixes and improvements.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.1" date="2026-02-26">
      <description>
        <p>Added Chinese, Japanese, Italian, and French translations. Performance improvements and error message cleanup.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.0" date="2026-02-24">
      <description>
        <p>Major version bump with new features and improvements.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.16" date="2026-02-23">
      <description>
        <p>Tray icon badge with active download count, dynamic window title, and mobile readiness improvements.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.14" date="2026-02-19">
      <description>
        <p>Telegram improvements: thumbnail previews with LRU cache, media search, and memory cleanup on navigation.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
